谢谢你帮我调整自行车弹簧了  帕克
Thanks for giving my bike a spring tune-up, Parker.
别客气  小哥
No problem, munch.
我要确保能把你从这里带走的东西
I wanna make sure the thing that carries you
时时刻刻都能正常工作
away from here is working at all times.
好了  小伙子们  清场了
All right, boys, clear out.
校队垒球选拔赛快要到了  我们要用后院来练习
Varsity softball tryouts are coming up, and I need the backyard to practice.
别想了  玛蒂  我们可是先到这儿的
Forget it, Maddie. We were here first.
乔伊你好啊
Hi, Joey.
我的天啊
Oh, dear.
整个后院就交给你了  玛蒂
Backyard is all yours, Maddie.
别急  我还没调整好呢
No, I wasn't finished!
整个后院就交给你了  玛蒂
The backyard's all yours, Maddie.
最好的朋友
Better in stereo
不同的朋友
b... b... better in stereo
迎着清晨阳光
- I'm up with the sunshine - Let's go
穿上舒服衣裳
- I lace up my high tops - Oh no
扣篮  热热身
- slam dunk - Ready or not
秀出你的份量
yeah, show me what you got
站在舞台中央
- I’m under the spotlight - Holler
准备下一场较量
I dare you, come on and follow
你有你的节拍
you dance to your own beat
我的歌声嘹亮
I'll sing the melody
你想接受
when you say yea-ah-ah
我却摇头
I say no-oh-oh
你想停留
when you say stop
我却一心只想  走走走
all I want to do is go, go, go
你  我最好的朋友
you, you, the other half of me, me
学不来的朋友
the half I'll never be-e
截然不同的朋友
the half that drives me crazy
你  我最好的朋友
you, you, the better half of me, me
离不开的朋友
the half I'll always need
你我有
but we both know
不或缺的朋友
we're better in stereo.
终于来了  终于来了
It's here! It's here.
我的未来终于来到了
My future is here.
我的未来就在这儿
My future is here!
夹在两片面包的中间
Between two slices of bread.
你的未来还早着呢
Your future can wait.
天啊
Look.
这不就是《太空狼人》里的道具服么
That's the costume from "space werewolves."
《太空狼人》可是一部一鸣惊人的动作电影
"Space werewolves" is a big action blockbuster
就像是下一部《暮光之城》一样
that's gonna be kind of like the next "twilight,"
除了主角是太空中的狼人而非地球上的吸血鬼
except it's werewolves in space instead of vampires on earth.
这个的可信度要高多了
It's way more believable.
所以  你得到了领衔主演的位置
So, you got the lead in the movie.
还没有  其实导演组认为一个姑娘看起来不够坚强
No. They actually don't think a girl will look tough enough.
所以你偷走了戏服
So you stole the suit
这样他们就拍不成电影了
so they can't make the movie.
你就这么心术不正啊
You are diabolical.
事实上  我跟他们说了要把狼人戏服寄给我
Actually, I talked them into sending me the werewolf suit
这样我就能拍照片来证明他们想错了
so I can take pictures in it to prove them wrong.
这样也成啊
That could work too.
我更喜欢心术不正的你
I like you better diabolical.
丽芙  大好消息
Liv, great news.
电视台第四频道刚打来电话
Channel four just called.
这周五他们要到咱家里
They're coming to the house this Friday
专门采访你
to interview you
来做他们的早间烹饪节目
for their morning news cooking segment.
我要上《尼比斯私房菜》了
I'm doing "Nibbling with Nimbus"?
对的 简直不敢相信
Yes. Can you believe it?
我爱死那个节目了
I love that segment.
上周  尼比斯和范·迪塞尔一起油炸了一只火鸡
Last week, nimbus deep fried a Turkey with Vin Diesel.
（范·迪塞尔：美国电影演员，制片人）
等等  妈妈  你刚刚说的是周五么
Wait, mom, did you say Friday?
又是《太空狼人》摄影
So a "space werewolves" movie photo shoot
又是一个直播电视访谈
and a live TV interview.
好了  这一周赶通告压力大咯
Okay, this is shaping up to be an oddly stressful week.
但是  幸亏你有一个超级酷的妈妈
Well, luckily you have a super-cool mom
还是一个可以帮你应付一切压力的治疗师
who's also a therapist. And she can help you manage your stress.
太好了  因为我马上需要你的帮助
Good. Because I am going to need your help
帮我挑出最上镜的那套衣服
picking out a TV-rrific outfit.
你需要我的时尚建议
You want my fashion advice.
天啊  这一天终于到来了
Oh, it's finally happening.
那好
Okay.
一件农妇衫
How about a peasant blouse
外加一条紧身裤怎么样
with some sensible trousers?
果然 找你要建议大错特错了
Yeah, this was a mistake.
绿带的学员们  掌握龙之真气
Green belts, the path of the dragon
绝非易事
is not easy.
嘿呀
Hyah!
别给吓趴下了
Do not be scared.
这苍蝇还活着  勉强算吧
The fly lives, barely.
我这么做的目的是杀鸡儆猴
But only so he can warn his friends
三心二意是绝对不可饶恕的
that distractions will not be tolerated.
天啊  蕾·道伊老师可不是闹着玩的
Wow, Sensei Rae Dawn is no joke.
我听说如果你直视她的眼睛
I heard if you look directly in her eyes,
她就能偷走你的灵魂
she can steal your soul.
小龙帕克
Dragon Parker,
你准备好通过释放出
are you ready to advance from green belt
你内在的龙之真气
to blue belt
来表演飞龙跳跃后空踢
by unleashing your inner dragon
把你的绿带升级为蓝带了吗
and performing the leaping dragon back-kick?
准备好了 老师
Ready, Sensei.
嘿呀
Hyah!
很令人钦佩 年轻的小龙
Impressive, young dragon.
这是你的蓝腰带
Your belt.
提醒一下你们的父母 新腰带价值 9.95 美元
Remind your parents it's 9.95 for the new belt
你踢烂的靶子价值 1.2 美元
and 1.20 for the target you broke.
小龙埃文
Dragon Evan,
- 你准备好  - 你先等等再说
- are you ready... - Let me stop you right there.
我妈说我今天还不能释放龙之真气
My mom says I can't unleash my dragon today.
什么
Excuse me?
她觉得我不能参加一个
She thinks I shouldn't participate in an activity
以成败评判小孩子的活动
where kids are judged in terms of winning or failing.
尤其是我失败已经板上钉钉了
Especially when I'm going to fail.
总之我今天能通过
Anyway I can get a blue belt
敞开心扉来促膝长谈
by being open about my feelings
而拿到蓝带么
and talking out issues?
看起来你内在的小龙更像是冒牌的蜥蜴啊
Seems your inner dragon is more of a salamander.
想拿腰带  没门
No belt for you.
你有一周时间来努力拿到蓝腰带
You have one week to earn your blue belt
要么就忍辱负重的看着班里其他人
or endure the shame of watching the rest of the class
挪到周二 2 点半的那节课
move on to the 2:30 Tuesday slot
就除了你
without you.
我绝对不能就这么让老师
There was no way I was gonna let the sensei
拆开我们
break up the team of
极品武术双人组
super-awesome martial arts dude
和他挚爱的老哥们
and his beloved sidekick,
雀斑  和嬉皮笑脸的冒牌蜥蜴
freckles, the smiling salamander.
耶
Yeah.
埃文也许要换一个新绰号了
Evan might need a new nickname.
好了  维罗  准备好了么
Okay, Willow, ready?
集中注意力  向我投球  就朝着这儿
Focus. Fire one at me. Right here.
太棒了
Perfect...
如果我们是在玩砸花盆的话
If we were playing "smash that pot."
维罗  你状态几天都不好了
Willow, you've been in a slump for days.
我只是不能全神贯注罢了
I just can't concentrate.
那好  垒球选拔赛就在这周末
Okay, well, softball tryouts are this weekend,
如果我们要成为校队里的首批二年级生的话
and if we want to be the first sophomores to make varsity,
你就必须得认真投入比赛
then you gotta get your head in the game.
你到底遇上什么问题了
What is your problem?
你知道吗  我一说起这事
You know what? I just don't feel comfortable
就浑身不舒服
talking about it.
那行  我们必须要趁着选拔赛前
Okay, well, we have to get to the bottom
把你所有的问题都消灭干净
of whatever this is before tryouts.
如果你不愿意和我聊天的话
And if you're not willing to talk to me,
也许我们就需要一些专业的帮助了
then maybe we need some professional help.
谁刚刚说了专业的帮助来着
Did someone say "professional help"?
这一天终于到来了
It is finally happening.
谢谢你们来到我的办公室见我
Thank you for seeing me in my office.
谢谢你开车带我们来
Thank you for the ride.
那是  我觉得在这了谈心会更加舒适
Well, I thought we would be more comfortable here.
而你们看见我所有的学历和证书时
And I thought you'd be more receptive to my words
也能更好的听进我的话
if you could see all my degrees.
总之  维罗不会投球了
So, Willow can't pitch.
对极了  治好她
Exactly. Fix her.
那么你就告诉我这幅罗夏测试图
So you tell me what is the first thing
（罗夏测试：通过墨迹图来反映被测者心理状况）
在你脑中最像什么
that pops into your head.
（墨迹图为左右对称，剧中测试方法不规范）
乔伊
Joey.
乔伊在骑一匹长得像乔伊的马
Joey on a horse that looks like Joey.
好了
Okay.
我看来要大胆推测
I'm gonna go out on a limb here
认定这其中肯定和乔伊
and say that this has something
有密不可分的联系
to do with Joey.
哇  你真在行
Wow, you're good.
乔伊
Joey?
这一切都是关于乔伊的
This whole thing is about Joey?
玛蒂  在这里我们要心平气和
Maddie, this is a safe place.
不要随意给别人下定论
We do not judge,
哪怕这是你脑中
even if it is the first place
第一个想去的地方
your brain wants to go.
那么你和乔伊到底是什么关系
Okay, so what is going on with you and Joey?
没任何关系  这就是症结了
Nothing. That's the problem.
正是春意盎然之时
It's springtime.
爱意弥漫在空中  鸟儿在枝头谈情说爱
Love is in the air, birds are chirping,
可我魂牵梦绕的一切就是
but all I can think about is
为何我的小乔伊不跟我谈情说爱啊
why doesn't my sweet little Joey bird chirp at me?
那到底乔伊和你的投球有什么关系
Okay, what... what does Joey have to do with your pitching?
我集中不了注意力
I can't concentrate.
当我投球时 我直视着你
When I pitch, I look directly at you.
- 对的  - 但我每次看你
- Right. - But every time I look at you,
脑中就浮现出乔伊
all I see is Joey.
我长得像乔伊  不可能
I look like Joey?! No, okay.
我们都戴眼镜
We both wear glasses,
可这就是唯一的相同点了  好不
but that is where the similarity ends, right?
对不
Right?!
所以你投球水平这么烂
So the reason you stink at pitching
责任在我头上
is because of me?
对  你们俩长得简直像极了
Yeah. You guys look exactly like each other.
只不过他才能打动我
Except he makes it work.
哦  太好了  你在这儿  我必须要找人聊聊
Oh, good, you're here. I really need to talk.
噢  我洗耳恭听
Oh, I'm all ears.
好的  维罗在低谷期  她投不了球
Okay, Willow's in a slump and she can't pitch,
这会让她进不了学校垒球队的
and that's gonna keep her from making varsity softball.
体育运动  我不在行
Sports.
但是她投不了球的原因
But the reason she can't pitch
是因为她无法全神贯注于任何事
is because she can't concentrate on anything
一心只有她对乔伊的疯狂迷恋
other than her massive crush on Joey.
哦  感情  这东西我在行
Ooh, feelings. Yay.
维罗是个好苗子
Willow's just so awesome,
我希望她能意识到大千世界除了乔伊以外
and I wish she would realize that there's so much more out there
还有无数的新鲜玩意等着被发掘
in the world for her other than just Joey.
那就让她看看大千世界的新鲜玩意啊
Okay, so make her see that there's more out there.
在她的储物柜里留一张匿名者的情书
Put a love note from a secret admirer
她就会把乔伊忘得一干二净的
in her locker, and she'll forget all about Joey.
丽芙  这个主意棒极了
Liv, that's actually a really good idea.
事实上  我还记得四年级时
Actually, I remember in fourth grade
当我沉湎于马基·斯蒂文而不能自拔时
when I was so obsessed with marky Stevens
我简直都玩不好儿童足球了
that I literally couldn't even play kickball.
之后我收到了一封匿名情书  写信的原来是
And then I got a secret admirer note from...
你
You.
之后谁在学校儿童足球赛
And who went on to win top prize
独占鳌头了啊
in the school kickball-y thing?
别说了  不用谢
Uh-huh, you're welcome.
- 你在干嘛呢  - 噢
- Whatcha doing? - Ooh!
别这么偷偷靠近我
Do not sneak up on me like that.
你在维罗的储物柜前干什么呢
What are you doing at Willow's locker?
更重要的是  我在维罗的储物柜前干什么呢
More importantly, what am I doing at Willow's locker?
那是一张留言条吗
Is that a note?
对  你千万别和任何人说
Yeah, actually, don't tell anyone,
但是我在帮我们俩一个忙
but I'm doing us both a favor.
这是一封匿名的情书
It's a secret admirer note
来帮维罗移情别恋
to get Willow to stop obsessing about you.
我希望你写好点
I hope you wrote a good one.
维罗犯的乔伊病已经病入膏肓了
Willow's got a bad case of the Joeys,
我还不确定有药能治好
and I'm not sure there's a cure.
唔  我脖子后边的汗毛立起来了
Hmm, the hairs on the back of my neck just stood up.
维罗要来了 快跑
Willow's coming. Run.
乔伊你好啊
Hey, Joey.
美女你好啊
Hey, beautiful.
这是什么
What's this?
有人喜欢我
Secret admirer?
哦不  不会吧
Oh-ho. No way.
看起来她相信了
It looks like she's buying it.
别学我这么站
Stop standing like me.
我们长得又不像
We do not look alike.
埃文  我知道你没拿到蓝带
Evan, I know you're disappointed
失望极了
that you didn't get your blue belt.
说实话  我挺好的
Actually, I'm cool.
我会把它看做我人生旅途的一部分
I've accepted it as a part of life's journey.
得了吧  埃文  我们是一队的
Come on, Evan. We're a team.
你不可能是这么想的
That can't be how you really feel.
你说对了  是我妈让我这么说的
You're right. My mom told me to say that.
你想象不到我以前都把什么看做了
You wouldn't believe the things I've accepted
人生旅途的一部分
as part of life's journey.
但我真的很想拿到蓝腰带
But I really do want my blue belt.
那我们就要释放出你的龙之真气
Then we've got to unleash your inner dragon.
你也听见老师这么讲了
You heard the sensei.
如果你下节课之前
If you don't become a blue belt
拿不到蓝带的话  我们就要甩下你调课了
by our next class, we move on without you.
嘿  别因为我水平差劲
Hey, just because I stink
就以为我听不懂人话
doesn't mean I don't understand English.
我们要让你足够愤怒
We are gonna get you angry enough
来释放你积攒已久的龙气
to release all your pent up inner aggression.
这是你妈让你带着的
This is the new balance plate lunchbox
营养均衡板午餐盒  对吗
your mom made you get, right?
但你想不想要酷到让人大跌眼镜的
But didn't you want the cool ufc lunchbox
终极格斗赛特款午餐盒呢
with the dude's eyeball falling out?
我妈认为那种太暴力了
My mom thought it was too violent.
再说了  这款有个胡萝卜暖瓶呢
Plus, this one had a carrot thermos.
埃文  如果你想要格斗锦标赛午餐盒
Evan, if you want that cool ufc lunchbox,
你就得把营养均衡饭盒砸了
you need to smash the balance plate.
来吧  伙计  深吸一口气再呼出点火苗来
Come on, dude. Reach down deep and breathe some fire.
你知道的  我还是别这么做了
You know, I better not.
我妈说如果我不把它带回家
Mom says if I don't bring it home,
我就吃不到甜品了
I don't get my dessert.
而你是知道我多喜欢生杏仁的
And you know how I love raw almonds.
丽芙  准备好《太空狼人》摄影了吗
Liv, you ready for your "space werewolves" photo shoot?
退后  愚蠢的人类  不然就尝尝我愤怒的滋味吧
Stand back, humanoid, or feel my fury.
哇  你看起来帅呆了
Whoa. You look awesome.
谢了  爸爸
Thanks, dad.
我们开始吧
Now let's do this.
咆哮
Snarl.
嚎叫
Growl.
再狂吠
Howl.
让我见识见识你的凶猛
Show me fierce.
砰  啪  咋样
Boom, pow, Wha-cha!
不
No!
爸  他们送来粘盔甲的胶水
Dad, the armor glue they sent me
应该是永久有效的啊
said it's supposed to be permanent.
别担心  趁你衣服没散架之前
Don't worry. I got some fantastic shots
我拍了几张顶好的照片
before your suit fell apart.
哦  太好了  这张真不错
Oh, great. That one's perfect.
现在我可以把痒痒的耳朵摘下来了
Now I can take these itchy ears off.
嗷
Ow.
它们卡住了
They're stuck.
噢 好吧 我的獠牙也卡住了
Oh, okay. So are my fangs.
真是奇怪
That's so weird.
他们送来的化妆胶水
The makeup glue that they sent me
写着说只有20分钟有效
says it's only supposed to last 20 minutes.
而粘盔甲的胶水写的是“永久有效”
And the armor glue says "permanent."
嘿  小玛
Hey, mads.
今天天气真不错啊
What a beautiful day.
我看见了心形的云朵
I see heart shapes in the clouds,
和闻起来像茉莉和热狗的空气
and the air smells like Jasmine and hot dogs.
我得到了一张匿名情书
I got a note from a secret admirer.
你真得到了
You did?
哇  刚才那真不是我们的风格
Wow, that's totally unlike us.
对  以后再也别这么做了
Yeah, let's please never do that again.
但是我不能不说我很吃惊
But I can't really say I'm surprised.
你这么一个顶尖的女孩
You are a top-notch lady
是每个男生都梦寐以求的
who any guy would be lucky to have.
现在就为进校队而努力吧
Now let's get us on that varsity squad.
把我的手打成肉酱吧
Turn my hand into a bloody pulp.
暗恋我的人是乔伊·鲁尼
My secret admirer is Joey Rooney.
我的小乔伊终于要和我谈情说爱了啊
My little Joey bird finally chirped back!
等等  乔伊
Wait, Joey?
那封情书和乔伊没有半点瓜葛
There was nothing in that note about Joey...
我这么说是因为那是匿名信嘛
I'm assuming because you said it was a secret.
好几个礼拜以来
For the first time in weeks,
我的思想终于清晰了  我能全神贯注了
my mind is clear and I can concentrate.
我是说  那明显是乔伊写的  对不
I mean, it's obviously Joey, right?
好吧  我知道我应该有权解释清楚
Okay, so I know I should have come clean
来保护我的哥哥
right then and there to protect my brother
和我最好的朋友的  但我的理由是
and my best friend, but in my defense...
好吧  我没啥可说的
Yeah, okay. I got nothing.
当然了  对的
Sure. Yeah.
怎么可能不是呢
Why not?
重点是你终于走出低谷了
The point is that you are out of your slump
现在我们能为选拔赛做准备了
and now we can get you ready for tryouts.
等下  这个嘛
Yeah, about that.
我以后不打垒球了
I'm quitting softball.
什么
What?!
维罗  你不能这么做
Willow, you can't.
情感是要耗工夫的
Relationships take work.
我和乔伊的情感发展
This thing I have going on with Joey
必须成为我的第一要务
has to be my top priority.
等会见了  小玛
See you later, mads,
如果我还能站定的话
if I ever come back down to earth.
哇
Wow.
看来她的乔伊病真的无药可治了
There really is no cure for a bad case of the Joeys.
年轻的小龙们  在我们给落后的埃文
Young dragons, before we give the weak link
最后一次赢得蓝腰带
known as Evan his final chance
的机会之前
to earn his blue belt,
花几分钟来喂饱你们内心中的猛龙吧
take a few moments to feed your inner dragons.
拜托这是零食时间  配合我一下好不
It's snack time. Work with me here.
我本打算放弃他  开始找一个新死党
I was about to give up and look for a new sidekick
但当我想起有一次埃文只是因为他妈妈给了他
when I remembered the time Evan lost it
海苔片而严重暴走
because his mom gave him seaweed chips.
所以我就把他的生杏仁
So I swapped out his raw almonds
都换成了恶心的水草
for some of that disgusting water weed.
至少我们还能最后一次在一起吃零食啊
At least we get to have snack together one last time.
你准备好吃零食了么
Are you ready for your snack?
你也该吃零食了吧
You should have your snack.
- 我其实还没那么  - 我说了让你吃零食
- I'm not really that... - I said eat your snack.
我不敢相信啊
I can't believe this!
怎么了啊
What's wrong?
居然是海苔片
It's seaweed chips!
新鲜的  有机的  海苔片
Unsalted, organic, seaweed chips.
我一直跟我妈说我恨死海苔片了
I keep telling my mom I hate them.
给我萝卜条或者芹菜
Give me carrot sticks or celery
哪怕是高丽菜也好  偏偏是海苔片
or even rutabaga, just not seaweed chips!
得了吧  哥们
Come on, dude.
听妈妈的话把它吃掉咯
Listen to your mom and eat it!
打死我也不吃海苔
I won't eat seaweed!
怎么了  看什么看
What, what?!
我真是个好朋友啊
I'm a good friend.
谁还想尝尝我的厉害
Who else wants some?
小龙埃文  这就是你的龙气啊
Dragon Evan, that was your inner dragon.
它被释放出来了
It's been released!
你已经准备好系上蓝腰带了
You are ready for your blue belt now.
太棒了  埃文  你成功了
Yes! Evan, you did it.
你小子别跟我讲废话
Tell me something that I don't know.
别被我甩下了  小子
Try to keep up, munch.
早上好  史蒂文斯波因特的观众朋友们
Good morning, Stevens point.
欢迎来到《尼比斯私房菜》
And welcome to “Nibblin' with Nimbus"
每一周  威斯康星周最受喜爱的气象学家
where every week, Wisconsin's favorite meteorologist...
也就是我  会给史蒂文斯波因特
this guy... cooks up some breakfast
最吸引人的住户或者游客做一顿早餐
for one of Stevens point's most intriguing residents or visitors.
而这周 除了美味的早餐
And this week, we got a tasty combination
我们还请到了
of breakfast brats
《放声歌唱》里的丽芙·鲁尼
and the always flavorful star
这个组合是不是会回味无穷呢
of “Sing Ot Loud," Liv Rooney.
我努力了整个晚上
I tried all night
来把我的狼耳朵和獠牙取下来
to get my ears and my fangs off.
它们固若金汤啊  我试着取消采访
They wouldn't budge. I tried cancelling
但是强尼·尼比斯还是准时出现了
and Johnny nimbus showed up anyway.
所以我做了任何好演员都会做的事
So I did what any great actress would do.
我把我歪瓜裂枣的地方都用戏服与道具藏好了
I hid my flaws with wardrobe and props.
现在出场的这位就是她了
Live and in person, here she is now.
哇  丽芙·鲁尼  这身行头不错啊
Wow, Liv Rooney, that is a nice getup.
告诉我  这几天孩子们都穿的像你一样么
Tell me, is that what all the kids are wearing these days?
若不是的话  看完节目他们就会了
'Cause if not, they will be after watching this.
啊  我在扯什么呢
Ah, who am I kidding?
我们的节目是没有孩子看的
No kids are watching this program.
强尼  你真是可爱啊
Johnny, you are adorable.
告诉我们  你今早要做什么呢
So tell us, what are you cooking up this morning?
好的  我会用平底锅来烤香肠
Well, I got a griddle full of brats
还要用与你加深了解做配菜
and a side order of get to know you.
哈
Huh?
很好 现在准备做水煎蛋了
Okay, now these eggs are ready for poaching.
这里分享一个从俺奶奶那儿学到的小窍门
And here's a secret I learned from Nana nimbus.
不要用水来煎  改用清鸡汤吧
Don't use water. Use chicken broth instead.
丽芙·鲁尼  你能帮我开一下么
Liv Rooney, could you open that for me.
- 好的  - 好极了
- Mm-hmm. - All right.
开好了 强尼
Here you go, Johnny.
哇 速度真快
Wow! That was quick.
很好  现在开始煎蛋了
All right. Now get poaching.
很不错
There you go.
就只要随意的把鸡汤倒进去
Just liberally putting it in there.
做好了就会非常美味的
They're gonna taste great.
很好 现在
Okay. Now.
来坐到桌前侃侃大山吧
Let's sit down to chew the fat.
照字面意思讲
And I mean that literally.
这些烤香肠九成都是脂肪
These brats are 90% fat.
快来吧 丽芙
Well, come on, Liv.
快来把你的牙深深地咬进
Come on over and sink your teeth
这些烤香肠里
into one of these babies.
我的亲娘啊
Oopsie-Daisy.
噢  丽芙  我来拉你起来
Oh, Liv, here. Let me help you up.
我的老天爷啊
Here... oh!
是我被咖啡灌糊涂了
Either I've had too much coffee,
还是狼人是真的
or werewolves are real!
呃
Um...
呃  没有啦  事实上  强尼
Uh, no. Actually, Johnny,
我只是给你们电视四台一个独家新闻
I am just giving you a channel four exclusive.
我将会成为《太空狼人》的主演
I am up for the lead in "space werewolves,"
所以为了让粉丝们小激动一下
so to get my fans excited,
我决定让你们先睹为快一下
I decided that I would give you a little sneak peek.
哦
Oh!
说实话
Seriously.
你差点把我吓尿了
You're kind of freaking me out.
嘿  维罗收到那张字条了么
Hey, did Willow get the note?
- 对  她收到了  - 她高兴么
- Yeah, she did, but... - Was she happy?
- 呃  其实她  -嘘  嘘  嘘  嘘
- Well, yeah, she was... - shh shh shh shh.
我只要知道她不会再粘着我了就好
All I needed to know is that she's off my scent.
你干的太漂亮了
You have served your purpose.
嘿  维罗
Hey, Willow.
维罗  维罗  维罗
Willow Willow Willow.
我听说你在储物柜里收到了一张小字条
I heard you got a little note in your locker.
我确实收到了
I did.
我打赌你挺兴奋的吧  哈
I bet you're pretty excited about that, huh?
我就说追随着彩虹总会发现你心所属的嘛
I say chase this rainbow and see where it takes you.
- 呃  乔伊  - 玛蒂
- Um, Joey... - Maddie.
现在别掺和
Not now.
我已经等这一刻
I've been waiting for this moment
等了很久了
for a long time.
我实在是憋不住了
I just can't take it anymore.
乔伊·鲁尼暗恋着我
Joey Rooney's my secret admirer!
到底发生什么了
What is happening?
哎呀
Yeah.
呃 我想我们仨最好
Uh, I think it's best that the three of us
找个安全的地方解释清楚吧
talk about this in a safe place.
维罗
Willow.
你可以放下他了
You can put him down now.
哦  我没意识到我抱着他
Oh, I didn't realize.
这感觉太美好了
It just feels so right.
谢谢你
Thank you.
狠狠地处罚玛蒂吧  妈妈
Punish Maddie, mom.
让她刷厕所连刷五年吧
Make her clean the bathrooms for the next five years.
对  处罚她
Yeah, punish her.
你们厕所的确还需要个帮手
Your bathrooms could use a little help.
我们一家六口住在房子里
There are six of us living in one house.
我已经尽我所能了
I do the best I can.
玛蒂  我听见的就是
Maddie, what I'm hearing
你哥哥和你极度专一的好朋友
is that your brother and your overly critical best friend
都自然而然的很不高兴
are understandably upset.
维罗  我只是想帮助你
Willow, I was really just trying to help.
我不想让我最好的朋友
I didn't want to see my best friend
整天对着一个傻小子神魂颠倒
drive herself crazy over some stupid guy.
呃  那个傻小子就坐在这儿呢
Um... The stupid guy is right here.
谢谢  玛蒂  但你不应该插手这件事
Thanks, Maddie, but you shouldn't have interfered.
我知道
I know.
我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
但你是个好姑娘
But you're a great girl
根本就不需要让一个男的来左右你的情绪
who so does not need a guy to make her feel better about herself.
千万别忘了
Never forget that.
你不会真的不打垒球了吧  对吗
You're not really quitting softball, are you?
不会的  你说得对
No, you're right.
我们要冲校队名额了
We're making varsity.
我不应该对一个傻小子牵挂这么久的
I shouldn't get hung up on what some stupid guy thinks.
又来  我在这儿呢
Again, right here.
所以玛蒂  你有什么想对你弟弟说的吗
So Maddie, is there anything you would like to say to your brother?
好的  乔伊
Yeah. Joey...
今早是你吃了最后那块松饼吗
Did you eat the last muffin this morning?
玛蒂
Maddie.
呃  我不应该让维罗
Uh... I should not have let
咬定了你暗恋她
Willow think that you were her secret admirer.
对极了
Exactly.
我和维罗彼此之间的感情问题
How Willow and I feel about each other
不关你任何事
is none of your business.
噢  不
Oh, no.
乔伊刚刚说了我们之间
Joey just said he and I had feelings...
对彼此有感情啊
About each other.
呃  不对
Um, no.
我的意思是  我先走了算了
What I meant was... I'm going now.
顺便  玛蒂  最后一块松饼是我吃的
And Maddie, I did eat that muffin.
把我藏好
Hide me!
我把埃文的龙之真气逼出来了
I unleashed Evan's inner dragon
现在根本收不回去了
and now I can't put it back in its cage.
帕克在哪里啊
Where's Parker?
我的猛龙想要把他乱丢一气
My dragon wants to throw him around some more.
我什么都不知道  小伙子
No idea what you're talking about, son.
老头  别想忽悠我
Don't lie to me, old man.
我看见他在你后面发抖了
I can see him trembling behind you.
我不是说过不能在屋里乱跑吗
What did I say about running in the house?
我不是说过不能乱搭话吗  女士
What did I say about talking back, woman?
站定  简直激动死了
Stop, drop and howl.
爸  《太空狼人》导演组来电话了
Dad, the "space werewolves" movie people called,
很明显  我的视频火了
and apparently my video went viral.
他们唯一比免费宣传更喜欢的
And the only thing they love more than all the free publicity
就是你拍的免费照片啊
were all the free pics you took.
我成功回到主演的候选名单了
I'm back on the short list for the lead.
我真为我的小狼人感到骄傲啊
I'm so proud of my little werewolf.
啊
Aah!
克制住你的龙  克制住你的龙
Cage your dragon! Cage your dragon!
嗨  埃文
Hi, Evan.
噢  对哦
Oh, right.
No wonder everyone looks me so wired at the mall.
怪不得在超市人人看我眼神都这么怪呢